Right, so in this project we're going to create our input and output data.
在此项目中 我们将创建输入和输出数据
So, for input data, we're going to count all the words that happen in a review,
对于输入数据 我们将统计评论中每个单词的出现次数
and then we're going to put them into a fixed length vector.
然后 将它们放在一个固定长度的向量里
Where each place in the vector is for one of our words of our vocabulary.
向量中的每个位置都对应词汇表中的一个词
So the first thing we do is we count our vocabulary.
所以 我们要做的第一件事 就是对词汇计数
Looks like we have just over 74,000 words.
大概一共有 74,000 多个单词
Now we're going to create our empty vector.
好 现在我们要创建空的向量
Now it's generally a good practice to pre-allocate this vector
通常 较好的做法是 预分配一个向量
as just something that's empty and then edit it as you go.
使其内容全为空 之后使用时再改变它的值
Because one of those expensive things you can do in
因为 分配新内存
computer science is allocate new memory.
对于计算机而言是一件代价高昂的事情
So we don't want to have to create this new vector from scratch every time that
我们不希望每次需要使用这个向量时
we use it.
都要创建一个全新的它
So we're going to create an empty one and then we're going to createa function
因此 我们先创建一个空的向量 再新建一个函数
that modifies this vector with the proper counts.
用于以计值来更新向量
So, first thing we need to do is decide which place in this vector goes to each
所以 我们要做的第一件事 就是确定向量中每个单词的位置
word, and create a variable that allows us to research that.
然后创建一个用于研究它的变量
Now, it doesn't really matter which place that we put it in, it's like,
事实上 单词放在哪个位置并不重要
horrible can be down here, or it could up there.
horrible 可以放在下面这里 也可以在上面
But as long as whatever we choose we kind of stick with, right?
只要我们始终选择同样的位置
So I'm going to create just a dictionary that allows us to look up every
因此 我会创建一个词典 可以让我们
word that's in our vocabulary according to the place that it has in that
根据单词在词汇表中的位置
vocabulary.
查找到每一个词
And then we're going to create our function.
然后 我们创建我们的函数
So layer here the global variable.
这里的 layer 是一个全局变量
We're going to clear out the old ones.
我们要清除掉所有旧的变量值
Then we're going to iterate through each word in our review.
然后对评论中的每个单词进行迭代
And we're going to allocate the position in that vector where we're incrementing,
对于向量中每个位置所对应的单词
so that there's a count for each one.
单词每出现一次 次数加一
Then we tried out in the first review, for the review 0 was this, right?
然后试一下第一条评论 就是 review[0] 对吧？
And it looks like it worked.
好像奏效了
Actually one of the words, presumably the empty one when I tokenized it,
实际上 其中一个单词 可能是我标记的那个空的
happened 18 times.
出现了 18 次
How about that?
怎么样？
So get_target_for_label seems to work, so
所以 get_target_for_label 看起来可以用
label(0) was positive, and label(1) I think was negative.
label(0) 为正 label(1) 我想是负的
So yeah, it looks like it's working great.
所以 看起来非常不错
S this will work great for us.
这个方法会很管用
This is our input and output dataset and
这是我们的输入和输出数据集
I hope that yours created kind of variables that look a lot like this.
希望你的网络也创建了类似的变量
The nice what we're doing here is, and I guess the thing to take away,
我们这里做得较好的一点 我认为大家能学到的
is mostly this efficiency piece, right?
最主要的一点就是高效率 对吧？
So when you're creating these vectors,
所以 当你在创建这些向量时
try not to allocate completely new vectors for your data.
尽量不要为数据分配全新的向量
The second thing that we're also not doing is pre-generating the entire
第二件我们没有去做的事 就是预生成
data set, right?
完整的数据集 对吧？
because that would be a matrix that is 74,000 by, how many train examples?
因为整个矩阵的大小是 74,000 乘以 多少个训练示例来着？
25,000, so 74,000 vocab_size x 25,000,
25,000  那就是 74,000 vocab_size x 25,000
that would be, man [LAUGH] around 2 billion integers.
结果是 [笑] 大约 20 亿整数
Which is just, that's a lot of stuff to store on your machine when, in reality,
如果都存在你的机器上 数量太大了 但实际上
we can populate this pretty easily.
我们可以很容易地填充它
And most of them are zeroes, and they're pretty quick we need to generate.
它们大多数的值都是 0 很快就能生成
So this is just generally good practice for
因此 这是一个很好的操作方法
creating your data set without filling up your RAM on your laptop.
又节省你的笔记本电脑内存 又能创建数据集
So, that's our input and output data set.
所以 这就是我们的输入和输出数据集
Those are kind of the things to watch out for.
这些就是你们需要注意的点
Don't allocate too much memory at once,
不要一次性分配太多新内存
and don't create new variables all the time.
也不要每次都创建新的变量
These are forms that we're going to use in our neural net, right?
这些就是我们将要在神经网络中用到的形式
So in the next section we're going to be talking about how we're going to put
下一部分 我们将讨论如何将学到的这些内容
this together into our neural network.
整合到神经网络中
See you there.
到时候见